The Feeding Never Ends
Haunt is a horror film directed by Mac Carter.
An introverted teen sparks with his new neighbor, and together the couple begins to
explore the haunted house that his family has unknowingly just purchased.
Janet Morello, played by Jacki Weaver.
Sam Richards, played by Liana Liberato.
Sara Asher, played by Danielle Chuchran.
Evan Asher, played by Harrison Gilbertson.
Alan Asher, played by Brian Wimmer.
Anita Asher, played by Ella Harris.
Dark House (also known as Haunted) is a 2014 American horror film directed by Victor
Salva and starring Tobin Bell, Lesley-Anne Down and Luke Kleintank.
The film follows a man named Nick Di Santo, who discovers that not only is his long-lost father
alive, but that he may be able to explain the source of his clairvoyant abilities.
The film explores themes of suicide, ghost, possesion, haunt.
The tone is dark.